sweepo.com 2018-05-15

# Casho

## Scope

Casho recognizes and respects your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to gathering information while you are visiting the Casho website and mobile apps, how we handle your personal information for our services and all further permissible uses of such information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective 7 days after being posted.

## Data Collection

You may visit Casho at any time without providing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit our website and mobile apps, we may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Casho, ad data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data.

For you to actively participate in Casho, we do need some of your personal information, however. Once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.

In connection with your registration and use of Casho, we may collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address, physical contact and personal information including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number;
  * all transactional information based on your activities on Casho;
  * shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping;
  * any correspondence sent to us or by us;
  * financial information, such as your credit card information; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties.

## Use of Data

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we and affiliates or members of our corporate group may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers;
  * provide you with special offers from our partners
  * contact you for market research; and
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

## Your Information on Casho

Once you have been approved as a registered user with Casho, you may be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout Casho and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Casho.

## Access, Review and Change of Personal Data

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Casho at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate.

## The Use of Cookies at our Website

Casho uses so-called "cookies", which are files that are stored on your computer or mobile device that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of "pop-up" windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, we would like to point out that turning off these settings may reduce the quality of your experience.

## Security Measures

Your Casho account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Casho will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Casho website; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations or share your PC with others. If you are using the Casho mobile app then we also recommend that you password protect your mobile device. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. As examples, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

## Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam

Casho assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

## Survey Serving Technology

This app uses Pollfish SDK. Pollfish is an on-line survey platform, through which, anyone may conduct surveys. Pollfish collaborates with Developers of applications for smartphones in order to have access to users of such applications and address survey questionnaires to them. When a user connects to this app, a specific set of user's device data (including Advertising ID which will may be processed by Pollfish only in strict compliance with google play policies- and/or other device data) and response meta-data (including information about the apps which the user has installed in his mobile phone) is automatically sent to Pollfish servers, in order for Pollfish to discern whether the user is eligible for a survey. For a full list of data received by Pollfish through this app, please read carefully Pollfish respondent terms located at https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent. These data will be associated with your answers to the questionnaires whenever Pollfish sents such questionnaires to eligible users. By downloading the application you accept this privacy policy document and you hereby give your consent for the processing by Pollfish of the aforementioned data. Furthermore, you are informed that you may disable Pollfish operation at any time by using the Pollfish "opt out section" available on Pollfish website . We once more invite you to check the respondent's terms of use, if you wish to have more detailed view of the way Pollfish works.

APPLE, GOOGLE AND AMAZON ARE NOT A SPONSOR NOR ARE INVOLVED IN ANY WAY IN THIS CONTEST/DRAW. NO APPLE PRODUCTS ARE BEING USED AS PRIZES.

## General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 2 days after they are initially posted.
